import { IFlashCard } from "./HomePage";

// prettier-ignore
export const mockData: IFlashCard[] = [
  { front: "評判", back: "評判（ひょう　ばん）fame; reputation; popularity" },
  { front: "指名", back: "指名（し　めい）naming; nominating; designating" },
  { front: "お得意さん", back: "お得意さん（お　とく　い　さん）regular customer; valued client" },
  { front: "朗らか", back: "朗らか（ほが　らか）cheerful; merry; sunny; melodious" },
  { front: "誠実", back: "誠実（せい　じつ）sincere; honest; faithful" },
  { front: "問わず", back: "問わず（と　わず）regardless of; irrespective of; without distinction of; no matter (how, what, when, etc.)" },
  { front: "お客さん", back: "お客さん（お　きゃく　さん）customer; client; shopper; spectator; audience; tourist; sightseer; passenger" },
  { front: "今朝", back: "今朝（け　さ）this morning" },
  { front: "仕入れ", back: "仕入れ（し　い　れ）stocking; buying up" },
  { front: "鉢植え", back: "鉢植え（はち　う　え）potted plant" },
  { front: "店頭", back: "店頭（てん　とう）shopfront; storefront; shopwindow; (near the) shop entrance" },
  { front: "位置", back: "位置（い　ち）place; situation; position; location" },
  { front: "季節感", back: "季節感（き　せつ　かん）sense of the seasons; feeling of seasonality" },
  { front: "配達", back: "配達（はい　たつ）delivery" },
  { front: "ご贔屓", back: "ご贔屓（ご　ひ　いき）favour; favor; patronage; favouritism; favoritism; partiality" },
  { front: "急いで", back: "急いで（いそ　いで）hurriedly; in haste; in a rush; quickly" },
  { front: "ご利用", back: "ご利用（ご　り　よう）use; utilization; utilisation; application" },
  { front: "藤", back: "藤（ふじ）wisteria (esp. Japanese wisteria, Wisteria floribunda); wistaria" },
  { front: "充実", back: "充実（じゅう　じつ）fullness; completion; perfection; substantiality" },
  { front: "囲む", back: "囲む（かこ　む）to surround; to encircle; to enclose; to fence; to wall in" },
  { front: "連日", back: "連日（れん　じつ）day after day; every day" },
  { front: "労う", back: "労う（ねぎらう）to show appreciation for (efforts, esp. by someone of equal or lower status); to thank for; to reward for" },
  { front: "常に", back: "常に（つね　に）always; constantly" },
  { front: "冷たい", back: "冷たい（つめ　たい）cold (to the touch); chilly; icy; freezing" },
  { front: "水仕事", back: "水仕事（みず　し　ごと）scrubbing and washing; kitchen work" },
  { front: "お伺い", back: "お伺い（お　うかが　い）inquiry; enquiry; question" },
  { front: "絶える", back: "絶える（た　える）to cease; to be stopped; to be discontinued; to be cut off" },
  { front: "方針", back: "方針（ほう　しん）policy; course; plan (of action); principle" },
  { front: "相談", back: "相談（そう　だん）consultation; discussion; discussing; asking (somebody) for advice" },
  { front: "慌ただしい", back: "慌ただしい（あわ　ただしい）busy; hurried; confused; flurried" },
  { front: "対応", back: "対応（たい　おう）dealing with; coping with; handling; response; reception; reaction" },
  { front: "休憩", back: "休憩（きゅう　けい）rest; break; recess; intermission" },
  { front: "来店", back: "来店（らい　てん）coming to a store (restaurant, bar, shop, etc.)" },
  { front: "遅め", back: "遅め（おそ　め）a little late; somewhat late; latish" },
  { front: "親子", back: "親子（おや　こ）parent and child" },
  { front: "連れ", back: "連れ（づ　れ）in the company of; accompanied by ...; as a group comprising ...​" },
  { front: "賑わう", back: "賑わう（にぎ　わう）to be crowded with people; to be bustling with​" },
  { front: "平日", back: "平日（へい　じつ）weekday; ordinary days (i.e. non-holiday)" },
  { front: "癒す", back: "癒す（いや　す）to heal; to cure; to satisfy (e.g. hunger, thirst); to alleviate (e.g. sorrow, fatigue)" },
  { front: "花壇", back: "花壇（か　だん）flower bed" },
  { front: "枯れる", back: "枯れる（か　れる）to wither (of a plant); to be blasted; to die" },
  { front: "土", back: "土（つち）earth; soil; dirt; clay; mud" },
  { front: "乾く", back: "乾く（かわ　く）to get dry" },
  { front: "職業病", back: "職業病（しょく　ぎょう　びょう）occupational disease" },
  { front: "腰", back: "腰（こし）lower back; waist; hips; lumbar region" },
  { front: "とも無く", back: "とも無く（とも　な　く）somehow; without knowing (it); unconsciously; unthinkingly" },
  { front: "集会所", back: "集会所（しょう　かい　じょ）meeting place; assembly hall" },
  { front: "奪い取る", back: "奪い取る（うば　い　と　る）to plunder; to grab; to snatch" },
  { front: "逃避", back: "逃避（とう　ひ）escape; evasion; flight" },
  { front: "迫る", back: "迫る（せま　る）to approach; to draw near; to be imminent" },
  { front: "準備", back: "準備（じゅん　び）preparation; arrangements; getting ready; provision; setup; reserving" },
  { front: "酔っ払い", back: "酔っ払い（よっ　ぱら　い）drunkard​" },
  { front: "絡む", back: "絡む（から　む）to pick a quarrel; to find fault" },
  { front: "お巡りん", back: "お巡りさん（お　まわ　りさん）police officer" },
  { front: "以降", back: "以降（い　こう）on and after; as from; hereafter; thereafter; since" },
  { front: "お勤め", back: "お勤め（お　つと　め）one's business" },
  { front: "頷き", back: "頷き（うなず　き）nod; inclination of the head" },
  { front: "深層", back: "深層（しん　そう）depths; deep level" },
  { front: "眺める", back: "眺める（なが　める）to look at; to gaze at; to watch; to stare at" },
  { front: "留まる", back: "留まる（と　まる）to stop (moving); to come to a stop" },
  { front: "姿勢", back: "姿勢（し　せい）posture; pose; position; stance; carriage (of the body)" },
  { front: "一礼", back: "一礼（いち　れい）bow (salute, greeting)" },
  { front: "去る", back: "去る（さ　る）to leave; to go away" },
  { front: "店先", back: "店先（みせ　さき）storefront; shopfront" },
  { front: "辺り", back: "辺り（あた　り）(in the) neighbourhood; neighborhood; vicinity; nearby; surroundings" },
  { front: "帰路", back: "帰路（き　ろ）one's way back; one's way home" },
  { front: "商店街", back: "商店街（しょう　てん　がい）shopping district; shopping street; downtown" },
  { front: "華やぐ", back: "華やぐ（はな　やぐ）to become brilliant; to become cheerful" },
  { front: "飛び切り", back: "飛び切り（と　び　き　り）best; extra-fine; superfine; unequalled" },
  { front: "何方か", back: "何方か（どなた　か）someone​" },
  { front: "通り", back: "通り（とお　り）the same status or way; as (e.g. as expected, as I said)" },
  { front: "花束", back: "花束（はな　たば）bunch of flowers; bouquet​" },
  { front: "手間", back: "手間（て　ま）time; labour; labor" },
  { front: "借りる", back: "借りる（か　りる）to borrow; to have a loan" },
  { front: "申し訳ございません", back: "申し訳ございません（もう　し　わけ　ございません）I'm sorry; (it's) inexcusable" },
  { front: "派手", back: "派手（は　で）showy; loud; gay; flashy; gaudy" },
  { front: "格好", back: "格好（かっこう）appearance" },
  { front: "繁華街", back: "繁華街（はん　か　がい）business district; shopping district; bustling street; shopping centre; shopping center; downtown" },
  { front: "言い合う", back: "言い合う（い　い　あ　う）to quarrel; to dispute" },
  { front: "険悪", back: "険悪（けん　あく）stern (expression); hostile (attitude); sharp; harsh" },
  { front: "状態", back: "状態（じょう　たい）state; condition; situation; appearance; circumstances" },
  { front: "手際", back: "手際（て　ぎわ）performance; execution; skill; dexterity; tact" },
  { front: "豪華", back: "豪華（ごう　か）extravagant; lavish; opulent; luxurious; magnificent; splendid; fancy; gorgeous​" },
  { front: "裏", back: "裏（うら）opposite side; bottom; other side; side hidden from view; undersurface; reverse side" },
  { front: "華道家", back: "華道家（か　どう　か）flower arrangement ​artist" },
  { front: "入荷", back: "入荷（にゅう　か）arrival of goods; goods received" },
  { front: "魅入る", back: "魅入る（み　い　る）to entrance; to possess; to enthrall​" },
  { front: "紫", back: "紫（むらさき）purple; violet​" },
];
